http://www.mediaminer.org/privacy.php

[FanFics]
[ New Forum ]
[ Register ] [ Login ]
Privacy Policy
MediaMiner Privacy Policy
This MediaMiner privacy policy describes the privacy practices for MediaMiner.
As part of our commitment to your privacy, MediaMiner has posted and maintains
our own privacy policy, you should read this policy if you intend to visit
MediaMiner.
Information We Collect
MediaMiner collects information about its users in a number of
ways. When you register as a MediaMiner user, you are asked to enter your name
and email address, and have the option to provide us with additional information.
We may also ask you for personal infromation when you join MediaMiner forum;
enter a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion, whether sponsored by us or one of our partners;
when you take one of our polls and when you ask to receive any of our newsletters.
While you are using the MediaMiner site, we automatically track
certain information about you, including the URL you just came from, the
next URL you go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We
also use cookies--pieces of information that Web sites transfer to your
computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes--on some MediaMiner pages to
keep track of your most recent visit to our site and to see if you have already
participated in various polls and contests.
How We Use Your Information
MediaMiner uses the information collected from you to better
understand the demographics, interests and behavior of our audience.
We do not share individual information about you with advertisers or
affiliates in the process.
Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Copyright MediaMiner 2000-2014 - [ disclaimer / privacy / contact ]
